Don't move.
Hey, friends.
Where are you folks from?
Just passing through.
Who are you people?
Just the two of you?
Your buddy here looks awful.
Looks like a bad injury.
Did you guys run into some trouble?
None of your business.
A Kuan.
Sorry.
I need to check your temperatures.
Just routine.
You're clear.
Don't be afraid.
We came out here
to
scavenge for supplies.
Our camp is just up ahead.
About a fifteen-minute drive.
Do you want to come
to our camp and rest up?
Appreciate the offer.
But no thanks.
We won't force you.
But if you don't treat that wound soon,
it's definitely going to get infected.
He's got a point.
Your wound really needs to be
properly treated as soon as possible.
Then, sorry for the trouble.
We're here.
Brother Dao is back!
I'm back!
Open the gate! Brother Dao is back!
Boys, unload the cargo!
You got it, boss!
What do you think?
This place
used to be a movie studio.
Everyone fled before the apocalypse.
We fixed it up a bit,
and turned it into a base.
Now there are dozens of us living here.
We've got elderly folks and kids.
We all look out for each other.
Thanks for your hard work, Brother Dao.
Good job out there.
Bet you didn't expect this.
We all used to work in the film industry.
As for me,
I used to be a producer.
That's Xiao Long.
He started out as a stuntman.
Lao Jiang is a prop master.
Sister Li, keeping busy?
- Hey, Brother Dao.
- Hi, Brother Dao.
Sister Li used to be our costume designer.
Everyone has their own talents.
Who knew they'd all come
in handy after the apocalypse?
Let me help you.
Brother Dao is
back! Oh, no need.
It's pretty heavy.
Thanks, Brother Dao.
Don't mention it.
I won!
Playing mahjong?
I'm out.
Just playing a bit.
Brother Dao.
Just finished working.
We basically don't keep freeloaders here.
Those who can fight go
hunting and keep watch.
Those who are good with their hands
cook and sew.
Hello, Brother Dao.
Hello.
That's our water storage area.
Water for laundry and
cooking all comes from here.
We also have some people
who can't do heavy lifting.
So we have them help watch
the kids and grow vegetables.
We all have to survive somehow.
This is the infirmary.
Hello, Brother Dao.
Feeling better? Remember
to change your dressing.
Will do! Much better.
Xiao Xi.
Make sure to get this
brother some antibiotics.
Okay.
You two can rest up for a few days.
If you want to stay long-term,
you'll have to pitch in
and work like everyone else.
After all, the resources here
were scraped together bit by bit.
No one gets a free ride.
Thanks, Brother Dao.
We'll just rest for a couple of days.
We won't cause you any trouble.
Alright, no problem.
Xiao Xi.
Help me settle these two brothers in.
Check the storeroom and see what
daily necessities they might need.
Please.
Follow me.
Doudou, ride carefully! Don't fall!
Your wound looks pretty bad.
I'll have Doctor He from
our base take a look at it later.
No need to trouble him.
No way, that wound needs to be
properly cleaned and disinfected again.
Could you grab some
iodine and gauze for us later?
Sure. If you need anything
else, just tell Brother Dao.
These two rooms are empty.
Take your pick.
One room is enough.
One room it is, then.
I'll have someone bring over
bedding and medicine shortly.
Okay, thanks.
"The Last Oath"
(Episode 14: The Final Performance)
Alright.
Lights out.
Everyone, please return to your rooms.
Lock your doors and windows.
Stay safe.
Lights out.
Everyone, please return to your rooms.
Get some sleep.
Stay safe.
Good night.
Sleep here.
Then behave yourself.
Just go to sleep.
Go to sleep.
The weather is so nice today.
Lin Zai!
Grandma Qiu!
Child, you're still alive!
Wait, Grandma,
what are you doing here?
A-Leh!
What happened to you guys?
We all thought you were dead.
Grandma, it's a long story.
A-Leh and I did go out
to pick wild fruit that day,
but we ran into some trouble on the way.
And then?
And then,
thanks to A-Leh,
he protected me the whole way.
Grandma, why are you here?
Where are Sister Chen and Brother Li?
I just got here two or three days ago.
After you left,
our base was attacked by zombies.
Chen Jin and Li Ming
protected me as we ran this way.
When we were almost at this camp,
we ran into a horde of zombies.
They hid me away,
and went to lure the zombies off.
They never came back.
Later,
the people from this camp found me,
and brought me back here.
Where did you separate from them?
Not far from here.
An abandoned industrial zone.
Let's go borrow a car and find them.
Don't worry, Grandma.
I'll bring them both back.
Be careful out there!
Come on, everyone, line up!
Thanks, brother.
Come on, grab it yourselves.
Take more if it's not enough.
Come back for seconds
if you're still hungry.
Grab it yourselves. Come on.
You're just in time. Food's ready.
Xiao Xi, get them two trays.
Hey, no cutting in line.
You have to go to the back of the line.
No need, Brother Dao.
We're not here to eat.
We have something to ask you.
Go ahead.
Grandma Qiu, who just arrived here,
used to be in our camp.
She got separated from two
others at the industrial zone.
We want to go look for them.
The industrial zone?
There are a lot of zombies over there.
Are you sure you want to go?
We have to, no matter how dangerous it is.
How about this?
I'll have A Cheng and A Kuan go with you.
They know that area pretty well.
No need.
You're still injured.
Just lending us a car will be enough.
You think you can just borrow it?
We're not running a charity here.
Brother Dao, we can pull our weight.
I'm good at fixing electronics.
A-Leh can stand guard.
Or scavenge for supplies.
Please, just let us borrow the car.
Thank you, Brother Dao.
Warning: Elevated heart rate detected.
Shut up, shut up!
A-Leh, did you just say something?
No.
Hurry!
It doesn't look like there
are any zombies around here.
What do we do?
There's a lot of them.
Conserve your energy.
Brother Li!
Rest in peace.
Lin Zai!